(Penny:)I remember you saying how great
it would be to have a first edition.
(Leonard:)It's true, I did. I did say that...
(Leonard:)...when we were at
the used bookstore together
(Leonard:)and I saw the first edition
and I bought it.
Oh my God, I am the worst!
No, no, ifs okay.
It's really thoughtful.
No, ifs not! I mean...
Whats thoughtful
is everything you do.
(Penny:)Here, you know what?
Look at this.
(Penny:)Look, here's the...
the plane ticket you bought me
(Penny:)when I was too poor
to go home for the holidays.
(Penny:)And the rose you left
on my windshield... just because.
Here's the thank-you letter
you wrote me
(Penny:)after the first time
I slept with you.
(Penny:)All 11 pages of it.
(Amy:)Can't believe
you saved all this stuff.
(Penny:)Of course I did. It's you.
(Leonard:)Come here.